[
    {
        "game_id": 1,
        "game_name": "ASL Alphabet",
        "content_module": "ASL", 
        "questions": [
            {
                "question": "hand",
                "answers": "Help Hold Hand None_of_the_above",
                "correct_answer": "hand"
            },
            {
                "question": "signal",
                "answers": "Scenic Signal Value None_of_the_above",
                "correct_answer": "signal"
            },
            {
                "question": "language",
                "answers": "Language Learning Document None_of_the_above",
                "correct_answer": "language"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "game_id": 2,
        "game_name": "LSE Alfabeto",
        "content_module": "LSE", 
        "questions": [
            {
                "question": "hola",
                "answers": "Hilo Hora Hola Ninguna_de_las_anteriores",
                "correct_answer": "hola"
            },
            {
                "question": "silbar",
                "answers": "Sentir Silbar Somera Ninguna_de_las_anteriores",
                "correct_answer": "silbar"
            },
            {
                "question": "luminosa",
                "answers": "Lamentar Librarse Limpieza Ninguna_de_las_anteriores",
                "correct_answer": "ninguna_de_las_anteriores"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "game_id": 3,
        "game_name": "Animal Kingdom (ASL)",
        "content_module": "ASL",
        "questions": [
            {
                "question": "elephant",
                "answers": "Giraffe Rhino Elephant None_of_the_above",
                "correct_answer": "elephant"
            },
            {
                "question": "penguin",
                "answers": "Duck Penguin Seagull None_of_the_above",
                "correct_answer": "penguin"
            },
            {
                "question": "kangaroo",
                "answers": "Wallaby Kangaroo Koala None_of_the_above",
                "correct_answer": "kangaroo"
            },
            {
                "question": "tiger",
                "answers": "Lion Panther Tiger None_of_the_above",
                "correct_answer": "tiger"
            },
            {
                "question": "dolphin",
                "answers": "Whale Shark Dolphin None_of_the_above",
                "correct_answer": "dolphin"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "game_id": 4,
        "game_name": "Animal Kingdom (Video)",
        "content_module": "GIF",
        "questions": [
            {
                "question": "dog",
                "answers": "Giraffe Rhino Dog None_of_the_above",
                "correct_answer": "dog"
            },
            {
                "question": "cat",
                "answers": "Duck Cat Seagull None_of_the_above",
                "correct_answer": "cat"
            },
            {
                "question": "bird",
                "answers": "Wallaby Bird Koala None_of_the_above",
                "correct_answer": "bird"
            },
            {
                "question": "wolf",
                "answers": "Lion Panther Wolf None_of_the_above",
                "correct_answer": "wolf"
            },
            {
                "question": "dinosaur",
                "answers": "Whale Shark Dinosaur None_of_the_above",
                "correct_answer": "dinosaur"
            }
        ]
    }
    
]